{
    "subject": "resource/Nina's_Heavenly_Delights",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "Pratibha Parmar",
    "human_readable": "Nina's Heavenly Delights was produced by Pratibha Parmar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9253000020980835,
            "question": "Who produced Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.878998875617981,
            "question": "When was Nina's Heavenly Delights produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8161734342575073,
            "question": "What is the name of the film producer who made Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7641360759735107,
            "question": "What film did Pratibha Parmar produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6732295155525208,
            "question": "Who might have acted in Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6054791808128357,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5714731216430664,
            "question": "What other films has Pratibha Parmar produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5506866574287415,
            "question": "Name a film by Pratibha Parmar."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5359434485435486,
            "question": "What genre is Nina's Heavenly Delights likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49493640661239624,
            "question": "Is Pratibha Parmar a filmmaker?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nina's Heavenly Delights was produced by Pratibha Parmar.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3507_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Nina's Heavenly Delights likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3507_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film by Pratibha Parmar.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3507_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other films has Pratibha Parmar produced?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3507_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3507_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3507_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3507_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3507_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3507_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3507_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3507_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3507_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3507_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3507_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all four files mention Pratibha Parmar as the director and/or producer of Nina's Heavenly Delights. For example, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3507/re-ranker-msmarco/76.txt mentions \"Nina's Heavenly Delights marks the feature film debut for director Pratibha Parmar\", and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3507/re-ranker-msmarco/67.txt mentions that \"The screenplay for Nina's Heavenly Delights was written by Andrea Gibb, based on a story by Parmar\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents indicate that Pratibha Parmar is the director of \"Nina's Heavenly Delights\" and not the producer. Therefore, the statement that Nina's Heavenly Delights was produced by Pratibha Parmar is incorrect based on the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Context states \"Nina's Heavenly Delights marks the feature film debut for director Pratibha Parmar, who also is producing the film.\"",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Pratibha Parmar is credited as the director of Nina's Heavenly Delights, not the producer. According to the context, she is producing the film alongside other individuals such as Marion Pilowsky and Chris Atkins.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}